Lewis W. Douglas papers, 1859-1974 (bulk 1880-1960)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Lewis W. Douglas Papers, 1906-1974
  - Subseries VIII: Organizations
    - Arizona Organizations
      - Miscellaneous Arizona honorary memberships and committees. no date (Box 366, Folder 10)
      - Social Clubs in Arizona. 1929-1974 (Box 366, Folder 11)
    - Social & Sports Clubs
      - Alfalfa Club. 1930-1973 (Box 367, Folder 1)
      - Alpha Delta Phi. 1927-1949 (Box 367, Folder 2)
      - Angler's Club of New York. 1955-1973 (Box 367, Folder 3)
      - Balboa Club de Mazatlan (Sinaloa, Mexico). 1965-1974 (Box 367, Folder 4)
      - Chevy Chase Club. 1943-1950 (Box 367, Folder 5)
      - Clove Valley Rod and Gun Club. 1962-1967 (Box 367, Folder 6)
      - Houghton Club. 1954-1974 (Box 367, Folder 7)
      - Jefferson Islands Club. 1931-1966 (Box 367, Folder 8)
      - Links. 1955, 1966-1967 (Box 367, Folder 9)
      - National Press Club. 1932-1933 (Box 367, Folder 10)
      - The Other club. 1958-1973 (Box 367, Folder 11)
      - The Thirty Club of London. 1958-1973 (Box 367, Folder 12)
      - Union Club. 1952-1958 (Box 367, Folder 13)
      - Wyandanch Club. 1955-1973 (Box 367, Folder 14-15)
      - Miscellaneous Social and Sports Clubs. 1927-1972 (Box 367, Folder 16)
      - Adirondack League Club (correspondence). 1927-1973 (Box 368, Folder 1-4)
      - Adirondack League Club (reports, membership lists, constitutions). no date (Box 368, Folder 5)
      - Adirondack League Club (maps). no date (Box 368, Folder 6)
    - Various, A-Z
      - Academy of Political Science. 1928-1972 (Box 369, Folder 1-5)
      - All Hallos Foundation, Inc. 1953 (Box 370, Folder 1)
      - American Institute of Mining, Metallurgical, & Peroleum Engineers. 1927-1970 (Box 370, Folder 2)
      - American Museum of Natural History. 1935-1974 (Box 370, Folder 3)
      - American Order of French Croix de Guerre. 1959-1973 (Box 370, Folder 4)
      - American Philosophical Society. 1958-1973 (Box 370, Folder 5)
      - American Shakespeare Festival Theatre. 1951-1973 (Box 370, Folder 6-8)
      - American Society of the Most Venerable Order of the Hospital of Saint John of Jerusalem. 1960-1974 (Box 370, Folder 9)
      - Artic Institute of North America. 1951-1973 (Box 371, Folder 1-2)
      - Association for Applied Solar Energy. 1954-1958 (Box 371, Folder 3)
      - Association for Applied Solar Energy/Solar Energy Society. 1959-1964 (Box 371, Folder 4)
      - Solar Energy Society/International Solar Energy Society. 1965-1972 (Box 371, Folder 5)
      - Barrow Neurological Foundation. 1960-1971 (Box 371, Folder 6)
      - CBS Foundtion, Inc. 1956-1959 (Box 371, Folder 7)
      - Chamber of Commerce of the United States. 1961-1969 (Box 371, Folder 8-10)
      - Child Adoption Service of the State Charities Aid Association. 1962-1967 (Box 371, Folder 11)
      - Council on Foreign Relations, correspondence. 1939-1974 (Box 372, Folder 1-7)
      - Council on Foreign Relations, memberships proposals by LWD. 1973 (Box 372, Folder 8)
      - Council on Foreign Relations, LWD's introduction to The U.S. in World Affairs. 1950 (Box 372, Folder 9)
      - Ditchley Foundation, correspondence. 1964-1973 (Box 372, Folder 10)
      - Ditchely Foundation, publications. no date (Box 372, Folder 11)
      - Employers' Liability Assurance Corp, Ltd., correspondence. 1951-1969 (Box 373, Folder 1-4)
      - Employers' Liability Assurance Corp, Ltd., Viscount Knollys. 1950-1966 (Box 373, Folder 5)
      - Foreign Policy Association. 1944-1968 (Box 374, Folder 1)
      - Foreign Service Educational Foundation. 1943-1947 (Box 374, Folder 2)
      - Former Members of Congress, Inc. 1970-1973 (Box 374, Folder 3)
      - Founding Friends of Harvey Mudd College. 1958-1973 (Box 374, Folder 4)
      - George C. Marshall Reseach Foundation, correspondence. 1960-1974 (Box 374, Folder 5-8)
      - George C. Marshall Reseach Foundation, dedication of the Library. May 23, 1964 (Box 374, Folder 9)
      - George C. Marshall Reseach Foundation, 20th Anniversary of the Marshall Plan. October 24, 1967 (Box 374, Folder 10)
      - George C. Marshall Reseach Foundation, photo album. 1972 (Box 374, Folder 11)
      - Hall of Fame for Great Americans at New York University. 1939-1973 (Box 375, Folder 1-3)
      - Institute for Advanced Study (Princeton, N.J.). 1940-1951 (Box 375, Folder 4-5)
      - Institute for Advanced Study (Princeton, N.J.), correspondence with Robert Warren. 1936-1950 (Box 375, Folder 6-7)
      - International Students Trust, correspondence. 1961-1972 (Box 375, Folder 8)
      - International Students Trust, publications. no date (Box 375, Folder 9)
      - League of Nations Non-Partisan Association. 1923-1929 (Box 375, Folder 10)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. 1961-1966 (Box 375, Folder 11)
      - Marshall Aid Commemoration Commission, Scholarship Advisory Council. 1958-1970 (Box 375, Folder 12)
      - Mining Club, Inc. 1964-1965 (Box 376, Folder 1)
      - National Bureau of Economic Research. 1945-1968 (Box 376, Folder 2-5)
      - National Conference of Christians and Jews. 1953-1974 (Box 376, Folder 6)
      - National Industrial Conference Board. 1943-1971 (Box 376, Folder 7-8)
      - National Foundation for Asthmatic Children of Tucson. 1954-1967 (Box 376, Folder 9)
      - National Institute of the Social Science. 1965-1973 (Box 376, Folder 10)
      - New York World's Fair 1964-1965 Corporation, correspondence. 1961-1968 (Box 376, Folder 11)
      - New York World's Fair 1964-1965 Corporation, correspondence regarding LWD's Churchill painting at the Fair. 1965 (Box 376, Folder 12)
      - Pilgrims of the United States, correspondence. 1941-1974 (Box 377, Folder 1-2)
      - Pilgrims of the United States, speech (dinner in honor of David K. Bruce). May 21, 1969 (Box 377, Folder 3)
      - Pilgrims of the United States, election of Douglas K. Beaton. 1970-1971 (Box 377, Folder 4)
      - Planned Parenthood, correspondence. 1962-1973 (Box 377, Folder 5)
      - Planned Parenthood, speech (testimonial dinner for Margaret Sanger). March 22, 1965 (Box 377, Folder 6-7)
      - Saint Andrews Society of the State of New York. 1946, 1960-1969 (Box 377, Folder 8)
      - Union Interalliee. 1970-1972 (Box 377, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous Organizations, A-G. 1927-1973 (Box 377, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous Organizations, H-Z. 1928-1973 (Box 377, Folder 11)
      - Organizations Memberships (honorary). 1949-1974 (Box 377, Folder 12)
      - Organization Memberships (lists). no date (Box 377, Folder 13)
      - American Legion (Arizona and National). 1926-1945 (Box 378, Folder 1-2)
      - American Museum in Britain, correspondence. 1961-1974 (Box 378, Folder 3)
      - American Museum in Britain, publications. no date (Box 378, Folder 4)
      - Royal Shakespeare Theatre & Shakespeare Theatre Trust. 1961-1973 (Box 378, Folder 5)
      - United States-South Africa Leader Exchange Program, correspondence. 1958-1970 (Box 379, Folder 1-4)
      - United States-South Africa Leader Exchange Program, publications. no date (Box 379, Folder 5)
    - English-Speaking Union
      - By-Laws, Boards, Committees. no date (Box 380, Folder 1)
      - Financial Records. 1945-1946 (Box 380, Folder 2)
      - Agendas, Minutes of Meetings. 1946-1947, 1955 (Box 380, Folder 3)
      - LWD elected to the Presidency. may 1946 (Box 380, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, general. 1940-1950 (Box 380, Folder 5-8)
      - Correspondence, NY and National boards controversy. 1946-1947 (Box 380, Folder 9-10)
      - Correspondence, general. 1951-1952 (Box 380, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, general. 1953-1958 (Box 381, Folder 1-5)
      - Correspondence, King George VI Memorial Fellowship Fund. 1952-1958 (Box 381, Folder 6-7)
      - Correspondence, Colombo Plan. May 1955 (Box 381, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, general. 1959-1973 (Box 382, Folder 1-7)
      - Minutes of meetings. 1959-1968 (Box 382, Folder 8-10)
      - 25th Anniversary Dinner, speech (Washington, D.C.). December 14, 1945 (Box 383, Folder 1)
      - Dinner, speech (NYC). December 10, 1946 (Box 383, Folder 2)
      - Dinner, speech (Chicago, IL). January 22, 1947 (Box 383, Folder 3)
      - Dinner, speech (NYC). November 28, 1951 (Box 383, Folder 4)
      - Dinner, speech (NYC). November 24, 1952 (Box 383, Folder 5)
      - Dinner, speech (NYC). November 23, 1953 (Box 383, Folder 6)
      - Dinner, speech (London). May 11, 1954 (Box 383, Folder 7)
      - Dinner, speech (NYC). November 3, 1954 (Box 383, Folder 8)
      - Dinner in honor of Anthony Eden, speech (London). July 7, 1955 (Box 384, Folder 1)
      - Dinner (NYC). November 26, 1956 (Box 384, Folder 2)
      - Dinner for Queen Elizabeth and Prince Philip (NYC), correspondence. January-December 1957 (Box 384, Folder 3-4)
      - Dinner for Queen Elizabeth and Prince Philip (NYC), guest lists, plans. no date (Box 384, Folder 5)
      - Dinner for Queen Elizabeth and Prince Philip (NYC), speech, program, clippings. no date (Box 384, Folder 6)
      - Dinner in honor of visitors and contenders for America's Cup Races (Newport, RI). September 19, 1958 (Box 384, Folder 7)
      - World Branches Conference of ESU, speech (Ottawa, Canada). October 27-31, 1958 (Box 384, Folder 8)
      - Royal Ball, sponsored by ESU-Pilgrims-U.S. Churchill Foundation (NYC). November 19, 1965 (Box 384, Folder 9)
      - Golden Jubilee Dinner, Phoenix Branch of ESU, in honor of LWD, speech (Phoenix, AZ). March 19, 1970 (Box 384, Folder 10)
      - LWD's articles for the Bulletin. no date (Box 384, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous memos and reports on Program and Policy. 1945 (Box 384, Folder 12)
    - Winston Churchill Foundation
      - Churchill College Trust Fund. 1958-1963 (Box 385, Folder 1)
      - Contributions. 1962-1964 (Box 385, Folder 2)
      - Appeals denied, undecided, no reply. 1962-1964 (Box 385, Folder 3)
      - Winston Churchill Memorial Fund, brochures, lists. no date (Box 385, Folder 4)
      - Winston Churchill Memorial Fund, correspondence. 1966-1968 (Box 385, Folder 5-9)
      - Winston Churchill Memorial Fund, national selection committee for travelling fellowship program. 1966-1968 (Box 385, Folder 10-11)
      - Winston Churchill Memorial Fund, minutes of meetings of executive committee. 1966-1968 (Box 386, Folder 1)
      - Winston Churchill Memorial Fund, Contributions. 1966-1968 (Box 386, Folder 2-3)
      - Winston Churchill Memorial Fund, appeals denied, undecided, no reply. 1966-1968 (Box 386, Folder 4)
      - Contributions, miscellaneous correspondence. 1970-1973 (Box 387, Folder 1)
      - Contributions, additional lists. 1970-1973 (Box 387, Folder 2)
      - Contributions, individuals A-Z. 1970-1973 (Box 387, Folder 3-11)
      - Appeals denied, undecided, no reply, indviduals A-C. 1970-1973 (Box 387, Folder 12-13)
      - Appeals denied, undecided, no reply, indviduals D-Z. 1970-1973 (Box 388, Folder 1-6)
      - Appeals denied, undecided, no reply, Sloan Foundation. 1970-1973 (Box 388, Folder 7)
      - Archives Centre, correspondence, gift charts, etc. no date (Box 389, Folder 1)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Aldrich, Winthrop). no date (Box 389, Folder 2)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Annenberg, Walter). no date (Box 389, Folder 3)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Astor, Mrs. Vincent). no date (Box 389, Folder 4)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Bingham, Barry). no date (Box 389, Folder 5)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Bruce, David K.). no date (Box 389, Folder 6)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Earle, Constance-widow of John G. Winant). no date (Box 389, Folder 7)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Ford, Henry, II). no date (Box 389, Folder 8)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Geffen, Maxwell M.). no date (Box 389, Folder 9)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Gifford, Walter). no date (Box 389, Folder 10)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Harriman, Averell). no date (Box 389, Folder 11)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Heinz, Henry J. II). no date (Box 389, Folder 12)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Houghton, Amory). no date (Box 389, Folder 13)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Josephy P. Kennedy Family). no date (Box 389, Folder 14)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Mellon, Paul). no date (Box 389, Folder 15)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Rockfeller, David). no date (Box 389, Folder 16)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Walton, Thomas J., Jr). no date (Box 389, Folder 17)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Whitney, John H.). no date (Box 389, Folder 18)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (Nieces of Frank Kellogg). no date (Box 389, Folder 19)
      - Archives Centre, contribution (various metal corporations). no date (Box 389, Folder 20)
      - Archives Centre, correspondence with Captain S.W. Roskill, Churchill College). 1970-1971 (Box 389, Folder 21)
      - Archives Centre, Opening ceremonies. July 26, 1973 (Box 389, Folder 22)
      - "Young Winston" Benefit Premiere (NYC), arrangements with Columbia Pictures. 1971-1972 (Box 390, Folder 1)
      - "Young Winston" Benefit Premiere (NYC), movie stills, brochures. October 10, 1972 (Box 390, Folder 2)
      - "Young Winston" Benefit Premiere (NYC), Men's Executive Committee. October 10, 1972 (Box 390, Folder 3)
      - "Young Winston" Benefit Premiere (NYC), Ladies' Executive Committee. October 10, 1972 (Box 390, Folder 4)
      - "Young Winston" Benefit Premiere (NYC), patrons. October 10, 1972 (Box 390, Folder 5)
      - "Young Winston" Benefit Premiere (NYC), honary patrons. October 10, 1972 (Box 390, Folder 6)
      - "Young Winston" Benefit Premiere (NYC), distinguished guests. October 10, 1972 (Box 390, Folder 7)
      - "Young Winston" Benefit Premiere (NYC), underwriting-food, flowers, theatre. October 10, 1972 (Box 390, Folder 8)
      - "Young Winston" Benefit Premiere (NYC), Royal Family (invitations to the Queen, arrangements for Duke and Duchess of Kent). October 10, 1972 (Box 390, Folder 9)
      - "Young Winston" Benefit Premiere (NYC), invitation, dinner program. October 10, 1972 (Box 390, Folder 10)
      - "Young Winston" Benefit Premiere (NYC), press, clippings, photographs. October 10, 1972 (Box 390, Folder 11)
      - "Young Winston" Benefit Premiere (NYC), correspondence and financial records. October 10, 1972 (Box 390, Folder 12)
      - Fenn, Roger C. 1959-1973 (Box 391, Folder 1-5)
      - Fenn, Roger C., correspondence regarding replacement. May 1970 (Box 391, Folder 6)
      - Senour, Roy R., Jr. 1970-1971 (Box 391, Folder 7-9)
      - Senour, Roy R., Jr., correspondence regarding replacement. 1971 (Box 391, Folder 10)
      - Epstein, Harold. 1971-1973 (Box 392, Folder 1-4)
      - Correspondence. 1959, 1963-1973 (Box 392, Folder 5-6)
      - Correspondence, financial. 1970-1972 (Box 392, Folder 7)
      - Financial Records. 1972-1973 (Box 392, Folder 8)
      - Brochure, annual reports (correspondence with Ogilvy and Mather). 1971-1973 (Box 392, Folder 9)
      - Brochure, annual reports (office correspondence, drafts, etc). 1970-1973 (Box 392, Folder 10)
      - Trustees, Gilbert, Carl J. 1958-1972 (Box 393, Folder 1-4)
      - Trustees, Hastings, Robert P. 1967-1974 (Box 393, Folder 5-10)
      - Trustees, Hawthorne, Sir William. 1970-1974 (Box 394, Folder 1-4)
      - Trustees, Colville, John R. 1962-1974 (Box 395, Folder 1-3)
      - Trustees, Cockroft, Sir John. 1963-1967 (Box 395, Folder 4)
      - Trustees, Davison, Daniel P. 1970-1973 (Box 395, Folder 5)
      - Trustees, Elliott, Osborn. 1970-1974 (Box 395, Folder 6)
      - Trustees, Gould, Laurence M. 1970-1973 (Box 395, Folder 7)
      - Trustees, Hay, Andrew M. 1971-1973 (Box 395, Folder 8)
      - Trustees, Killian, James R. 1969-1973 (Box 395, Folder 9)
      - Trustees, Knollys, Viscount. 1958-1963 (Box 395, Folder 10)
      - Trustees, Larmon, Sigurd S. 1970-1973 (Box 395, Folder 11)
      - Trustees, Lazarus, Ralph. 1966, 1971-1974 (Box 395, Folder 12)
      - Trustees, Loeb, John L. 1970-1973 (Box 395, Folder 13)
      - Trustees, Reed, Philip D. 1970-1973 (Box 395, Folder 14)
      - Trustees, Roosevelt, Franklin D., Jr. 1972-1973 (Box 395, Folder 15)
      - Trustees, Soames, Lady Mary. 1971-1974 (Box 395, Folder 16)
      - Trustees, Spaght, Monroe E. 1971-1973 (Box 395, Folder 17)
      - Trustees, Ward, Hugh C. 1970-1974 (Box 395, Folder 18)
      - Trustees, correspondence. 1970-1973 (Box 395, Folder 19)
      - Honorary Trustees, Lady Spencer-Churchill. 1961, 1970-1973 (Box 396, Folder 1)
      - Honorary Trustees, Winston Churchill, M.P. 1970-1973 (Box 396, Folder 2)
      - Honorary Trustees, H.R.H. Prince Philip. 1970-1973 (Box 396, Folder 3)
      - Honorary Trustees, Dwight D. Eisenhower and Mrs. Eisenhower. 1965-1966, 1970-1973 (Box 396, Folder 4)
      - Honorary Trustees, Harry S. Truman and Mrs. Truman. 1965-1972, 1972-1973 (Box 396, Folder 5)
      - Trustees, financial statements. 1963-1972 (Box 397, Folder 1)
      - Trustees, board of trustees meetings. 1970-1974 (Box 397, Folder 2-10)
      - Legal Correspondence, Taylor, Willard. 1970-1972 (Box 398, Folder 1-2)
      - Legal Correspondence, Fenton, Wendell. 1970-1974 (Box 398, Folder 3-4)
      - Legal Correspondence, certicicate of Incoroporation and By-Laws. 1958-1970 (Box 398, Folder 5)
      - Scholarships & Fellowships, Churchill Scholarships (brochures, announcements, etc). no date (Box 399, Folder 1)
      - Scholarships & Fellowships, Cambridge Admissions Prospectus. 1973/1974 (Box 399, Folder 2)
      - Scholarships & Fellowships, lists. no date (Box 399, Folder 3)
      - Scholarships & Fellowships, correspondence. 1968-1973 (Box 399, Folder 4-7)
      - Anniversary Dinner (NYC), correspondence, plans. 1970-1971 (Box 400, Folder 1-2)
      - Anniversary Dinner (NYC), correspondence (regrets & acceptances). March 31, 1971 (Box 400, Folder 3-6)
      - Anniversary Dinner (NYC), correspondence. March 31, 1971 (Box 400, Folder 7)
      - Anniversary Dinner (NYC), invitation list. March 31, 1971 (Box 400, Folder 8)
      - Anniversary Dinner (NYC), photographs, clippings, etc. March 31, 1971 (Box 400, Folder 9)
      - Proposed 1974 Centennial, George Trescher. 1973 (Box 401, Folder 1)
      - Proposed 1974 Centennial, correspondence. 1972-1974 (Box 401, Folder 2)
      - Proposed 1974 Centennial, correspondence (committee). 1972-1974 (Box 401, Folder 3)
      - Proposed 1974 Centennial, Julio fiocci, proposed pistol reproduction. no date (Box 401, Folder 4)
      - Proposed 1974 Centennial, Franklin Mint, Churchill Medallion. no date (Box 401, Folder 5)
      - Proposed 1974 Centennial, Library of Imperial History, Centennial Edition of Churchill's Collected Works. no date (Box 401, Folder 6)
      - Proposed 1974 Centennial, Rand McNally, pictoral book about Churchill. no date (Box 401, Folder 7)
      - Churchill College, miscellaneous material. no date (Box 402, Folder 1)
      - Churchill College, correspondence with Major General J.R.C. Hamilton, Bursar. 1961, 1971-1972 (Box 402, Folder 2)
      - Churchill College, correspondence with Kenneth McQuillen, Vice-Master. 1971-1973 (Box 402, Folder 3)
      - Churchill College, miscellaneous photographs. no date (Box 402, Folder 4)
      - Churchill College, Churchill Review. 1969, 1971-1973 (Box 402, Folder 5)
      - Winston Churchill Foundation of the United States, Annual Report. 1971-1972 (Box 402, Folder 6)
      - "Churchilliana." no date (Box 402, Folder 7)
      - Westminster College, correspondence with President R. Davidson and others. 1962-1973 (Box 403, Folder 1)
      - Westminster College, correspondence with Brom Ault. 1970-1972 (Box 403, Folder 2)
      - Westminster College, proposed bill of Patrick Jenkin, M.P. 1971 (Box 403, Folder 3)
      - Westminster College, Commencement. May 21, 1972 (Box 403, Folder 4)
      - Westminster College, miscellaneous material. no date (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - Memorial Hospital & Alfred P. Sloan Foundation
      - Memorial Hospital, NYC. 1931-1971 (Box 404, Folder 1-4)
      - Alfred P. Sloan Foundatio. 1944-1973 (Box 404, Folder 5-9)
      - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation. 1967 (Box 404, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller Foundation
      - Correspondence, minutes of meetings, and financial reports. 1934-1970, 1935-1939 (Box 405)
      - Confidential Montly Reports. 1937-1939 (Box 406)
      - Dockets of Meetings. 1935-1939 (Box 407)
      - Executive Committee Meetings: Dockets. January 1936-May 1937 (Box 408)
      - Executive Committee Meetings: Dockets. June 1938-November 1939 (Box 409)
      - General Education Board Meetings: Dockets. 1939 (Box 409)
      - Quarterly Bulletin. October 1935-October 1936 (Box 409)
      - Declinations. 1936-1939 (Box 410)
      - Scientific Directors Meeting. November 1935 (Box 410)
      - Miscellaneous reports. no date (Box 410)
      - Trubee Davison, Jr., Memorial Fund (cancer researh). 1939 (Box 410)
      - Miscellaneous Material. no date (Box 410)
    - General Motors
      - Correspondence. 1944-1959 (Box 411, Folder 1-5)
      - By-Laws, organization charts, clippings. no date (Box 411, Folder 6)
      - Securities and Exchange Commission Reports on Haskins and Sells Case. 1950-1952 (Box 411, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence. 1960-1973 (Box 412, Folder 1-8)
      - Miscellaneous publications. no date (Box 412, Folder 9)
  - Subseries IX: Mutual Life Insurance
    - Correspondence
      - Appointment as President. 1939-1940 (Box 413, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence and Memoranda. 1939 (Box 413, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous. 1940-1955 (Box 413, Folder 3-9)
      - Miscellaneous. 1956-1973 (Box 414, Folder 1-10)
      - Portrait of LWD. 1962-1966 (Box 414, Folder 11)
      - W. Marshall Bullitt. 1938-1939, 1944-1957 (Box 415, Folder 1-3)
      - Louis Dawson. 1941, 1947-1963 (Box 415, Folder 4-7)
      - Henry S. Kingman. 1947-1949 (Box 415, Folder 8)
      - Alexander Patterson. 1943-1948 (Box 415, Folder 9)
      - Gilbert H. Scribner. 1945-1949 (Box 415, Folder 10)
      - Leo Wolman. 1945-1955 (Box 416, Folder 1)
      - donald B. Woodward. 1939-1956 (Box 416, Folder 2-3)
      - "Stern Matter." 1941-1944 (Box 416, Folder 4)
      - Eugene C. Pulliam & William R. Mathews. 1946 (Box 416, Folder 5)
      - Francis Stone. 1946 (Box 416, Folder 6)
      - E.F. Hutton Newspaper Ad. 1946 (Box 416, Folder 7)
      - Samp Applewhite and Phillips B. Shaw. 1941, 1946 (Box 416, Folder 8)
      - LWD's Annual Report. 1941 (Box 416, Folder 9)
      - LWD personal miscellanyu. no date (Box 416, Folder 10)
    - Historical Material and Reports
      - Historical material from W.A. Hutcheson. 1940 (Box 417, Folder 1)
      - Mailing lists for book on the company's history. 1945 (Box 417, Folder 2)
      - President's Report to Trustees. 1944, 1946 (Box 417, Folder 3)
      - Department Reports. 1939, 1940, 1943 (Box 417, Folder 4-8)
      - Department Reports. 1944-1947 (Box 418, Folder 1-4)
      - 2 notebooks on The Guertin Legislation and Changes Necessary After January 1, 1948. 1947 (Box 418)
    - Topics
      - Advertising (John Price Jones Report). 1940 (Box 419, Folder 1)
      - Agents' shortages. no date (Box 419, Folder 2)
      - Audit. 1938-1947 (Box 419, Folder 3-4)
      - Audit (triennial examination by insurance department). no date (Box 419, Folder 5)
      - Budget. no date (Box 419, Folder 6)
      - "City Rating and Regional Selction." 1940 (Box 419, Folder 7)
      - Comparisons. no date (Box 419, Folder 8)
      - Dividends, basic scale and proposed revision. no date (Box 420, Folder 1)
      - Dividends, distribution on disability policies. no date (Box 420, Folder 2)
      - dividends, first year. no date (Box 420, Folder 3)
      - Foreign Affairs. no date (Box 420, Folder 4)